Alex Fallaw

Graphic Designer

I'm a graphic design student at the University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign. I've been passionate about art for almost a decade, experimenting with several different art forms over the years. I've recently gotten into coding, and I love the problem-solving and graphic design involved in coding a website. I'm looking for an internship or entry-level job in web or graphic design.

Skill Highlights

- Digital design
- Instructional graphic design
- Website design
- Wireframing
- Collaborative story writing
- Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, InDesign)
- Figma

- SketchBook
- WordPress
- ♦ HTML
- CSS
- Java
- JavaScript
- ❖ React JS

Education

- University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign
 Graphic Design, BFA with minor in Computer Science
 2022-present
- University of Wisconsin Eau Claire Graphic Communications 2021-2022
- Parkland College General Studies 2020-2021

Work Experience

Lowes Cashier

- * Responsibilities:
 - Deliver excellent customer service at the register
 - Answer customer questions
- May 2021 August 2021
- Location: Champaign, IL
- Was awarded a service award for customer service

House Cleaner

- Responsibilities:
 - Dishes
 - Vacuuming
 - General cleaning
- ❖ December 2019 August 2021
- Location: Champaign, IL